#### **NABIL FANNANE**

+1 (415) 574-7713 mzabi30@gmail.com https://mzabicoder.github.io/ModernPortfolio

Creative web developer and communication professional, specialized in Object- Oriented Programming and design, with the ability to adapt to new emerging technologies. Firsthand knowledge in web application building from the design to deployment

# **Technical Skills**

- ✓ HTML/CSS/SASS
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ FlexBox/Grid
- ✓ TypeScript

- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ React/Angular
- ✓ ExpressJS
- Mongoose
- ✓ NodeJS/Jest
- ✓ NPM/Yarn/Git/GitHub
- ✓ MongoDB/PostgreSQL
- ✓ MaterializeCSS/Reactstrap/Material-UI

#### **EXPERIENCE**

IBM (August 2021 - Current) UI Engineer

San Jose, CA,

- Create websites and user interfaces, using standard JS/REACT/HTML/SASS practices, while incorporating data from back-end services.
- Consistency create well-designed, tested code using best practices for website development.
- A clear understanding of modern digital marketing capabilities.
- Perform UI/UX designs and coding, create reusable objects, expansions, and scaling of each design

Costar Group (Nov 2020 – August 2021)

San Francisco, CA,

Front End Engineer

- Handle user stories & tasks Using Azure (TFS)
- Create reusable modules & components for re-platforming www.bizbuysell.com
- Par Create detailed documentations for new features.

### **INFOMATUM LLC** (*Jun 2014 – Oct 2017*)

San Francisco, CA

IT&Web Analyst

- Co-working venues and display pictures & information about them upon click
- Design the layout and visual of the site using (CSS3,Grid,Flex,Bootstrap)
- Part of a 3-member team providing IT solutions to small business clients across the Bay Area
- Install, configure and troubleshoot network-level WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity, DNS, DHCP, VPN
- Imaging new PCs with Acronix and MACs with Deploy-studio, Manage & set up Duo two-factor authenti

## ATTACK!! (Nov 2011 – Oct 2013)

Desktop Engineer

### San Francisco, CA

- Member of in-house IT team for a relationship marketing company with offices in California and New York
- Install, configure and troubleshoot laptops, workstations, printers and IP-phones. Manageandset up Cisco phone users
- Troubleshoot and configure DNS, DHCP, VPN, HTTP, AD administration Windows server 2003/2008, Windows XP/7/8, Thunderbird, Outlook, Google Applications and Office 2010
- Configure&troublshoot WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity including remote connection using LogmeIn,gotomeeting
- Create and maintain user accounts, passwords, data integrity, system access and security fordesktop technologies

# STM icroelectronics (Sep 2009-jun 2011)

Casa, Morocco

**Production Engineer** 

- Co-working venues and display pictures & information about them upon click
- Design the layout and visual of the site using (CSS3,Grid,Flex,Bootstrap)
- Part of a 3-member team providing IT solutions to small business clients across the Bay Area
- Install, configure and troubleshoot network-level WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity, DNS, DHCP, VPN
- Imaging new PCs with Acronix and MACs with Deploy-studio, Manage & set up Duo two-factor authenti

#### **EDUCATION**

## MOROCCAN SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING(2003-2008)

Casa, Morocco

- Co-working venues and display pictures & information about them upon click
- Design the layout and visual of the site using (CSS3,Grid,Flex,Bootstrap)
- Part of a 3-member team providing IT solutions to small business clients across the Bay Area
- Install, configure and troubleshoot network-level WAN/LAN TCP/IP connectivity, DNS, DHCP, VPN
- Imaging new PCs with Acronix and MACs with Deploy-studio, Manage & set up Duo two-factor authenti